tell me what's different
何が違うか教
Please get it.
えて ください
What's the difference?
何が違う?
Which one is bigger in his size?
彼の大きさはどっちが大きい?
Was he small again?
また彼が小さかったの?
Be honest.
正直に言えなさい
What's the shape?
形は?
What shape did it have?
どういう形したの?
How is it different?
どういう風に違うの?
Are you smoking?
吸ってんの?
吸 ってんの?
What do you mean by smoking?
吸 って ん の?
this.
これ
When I smoked it, the upper part became normal.
吸ってやると上の方が 正常になった時ね
Because it will rub.
擦れるからさ
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいかな?
Did you want to say it?
言えたくなった?
Together while licking.
舐めながら一緒に
Turn to the other side.
向こうに向いて
Have you ever licked it?
舐 めたことある?
this.
これ
Have you ever licked your boyfriend?
彼氏と舐めたことある?
More with him.
もっと彼と
be?
ある?
I wish I could just say it.
言っちゃっていいんだけどね
I said let's go for a ride.
乗ってみようかって言って
yes.
はい
like this?
こう?
Take it out.
出してね
Please bring it out again.
また出してね
Take it out.
出して
Picha Picha.
ピチャピチャ
I'm talking picha picha.
ピチャピチャ言ってる
Are you talking picha picha?
ピチャピチャ言ってるの?
I have to go chin chin.
チンチンとか行かないとね
I don't like it.
嫌だ
what happened?
どうしたの?
Did you pull it out?
抜いちゃったの?
Put it in, put it in.
入れて、入れて
You can press it properly when you go.
行くとき押せるね、ちゃんと
what happened?
どうしたの?
I'm not doing anything.
何もしてないよ
I like it.
僕好きなんだよ
Even if you're not doing anything.
何もしてなくても
do anything
何 も して
do not have.
ない
It feels good because it's raw, right?
生 だから気持ちいいのなんでしょ?
it hurts.
痛い
It feels good, right?
気持ちいいでしょ?
The back part has also endured, right?
後ろのところも耐えてきたでしょ?
Let's touch it.
触ってみよう
good?
いい?
Feels good
気持ちいい
hey.
ね
It's starting to look like ya.
や らしくなったね
I put it in.
入れちゃったんだ
You couldn't get in at first, right?
最初入れなかったでしょ?
I'm glad I did it, right?
やって よかったでしょ?
Even if you're not doing anything.
何もしてなくても
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
You can't do it, can you?
できないでしょ?
Can you lick it?
舐めれる?
Let me know if it's not possible.
無理だったら言って
Open the mango.
マンゴー開いて
Are you sleeping?
寝てる?
You may not be able to see your pussy.
おまなが見えないかもし
Not possible.
れない
I don't cry.
泣 くない
It's sneaky.
ずるいよ
You can come visit us again.
また寄りに来られる
You won't go back to elementary school, right?
小学期に帰さないでしょ?
It's not enough, right?
足りないでしょ?
It feels good.
気持ちいいもんね
It felt so good.
気 持ちよくてこんなに
I wish I could serialize it in elementary school.
小学期に連載できたら
That's fine.
いいじゃん
Can you come again?
また来られる?